First Last

NB: The Summary section is completely optional. Your resume is already a summary of your accomplishments and you usually should not re-summarize it in paragraph form. However, if you have valuable experience that doesn't fit in your experience section below (e.g. you're changing careers), it can be useful to include one. Visit Resume Worded.com for details on exactly what to include in your resume.

San Francisco, CA 12345 +1 234 567-890

<u>first.last@resumeworded.com</u> linkedin.com/in/resumeworded

EXPERIENCE

Resume Worded, New York, NY Data Analyst (Revenue Team)

January 2020 - Present

- Analyzed data from 25000 monthly active users and used outputs to guide marketing and product strategies; increased average app engagement time by 2x and decreased drop off rate by 30%
- Cut projected time for data analysis by one week by developing reusable ETL components using Pentaho Kettle
- Designed merchandising strategies for grocery retailers based on regression analysis identifying key store attributes to increase traffic and conversion; resulted in a 25% sales lift
- Identified changes to assortment, distribution, and marketing using financial and behavioral analysis that enabled an upmarket fashion company to better target their customers, resulting in \$1M growth
- Bullet points should be in format [Action Verb] [Accomplishment] [Metric]

My Exciting Company, Remote

Operations Analyst

July 2016 - January 2020, New York, NY

- Led the transition to a paperless practice by implementing an electronic booking system and a faster, safer and more accurate business system; reduced cost of labor by 30% and office overhead by 10%
- Spearheaded a major pricing restructure by redirecting focus on consumer willingness to pay instead of product cost; implemented a three-tiered pricing model which increased average sale 35% and margin 12%
- Coached 30 summer interns and launched a mentorship program for new joiners in the Berlin office

Resume Worded, Boston, MA

Iob Title

January 2012 - June 2016, New York, NY

- Designed, executed, and optimized digital marketing campaign on Google AdWords; led to 20% increase in ROI
- Managed redevelopment of internal tracking system in use by 125 employees, resulting in 20+ new features, reduction of 20% in save/load time and 15% operation time
- Bullet points should be in format [Action Verb] [Accomplishment] [Metric]

SKILLS

Advanced in Excel & Google Sheets and HTML/CSS

Proficient in MATLAB

[Be sure to include 3-5 skills from the job description that you have]

EDUCATION

Resume Worded University

B.S. in Business Management, Minor in Data Analytics

January 2012

New York, NY

- Awards: Resume Worded Teaching Fellow (only 5 awarded to class), Dean's List 2012 (Top 10%)
- Relevant Courses:
 Operations Research,
 Statistics, Linear Algebra
- Completed one-year study abroad with Singapore University

PROJECTS

- Aggregated, cleansed and combined data from 10+ public data sources to create a Tableau dashboard of inflation rates over the past 10 years (January 2021)
- Another project -optional